Guide to the Records of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center RG.42.5
New York University Archives
- Series II: Administrative Files, 1961-1988
  - Subseries D: Development, 1964-1980
    - Bay Area -- Project Budget, 1984 (Box II:5, Folder 62)
    - Bay Area Painting -- Shipping Arrangements, 1984 February-September (Box II:5, Folder 63)
    - Bay Area Painting -- Dispersal, 1984 March-August (Box II:5, Folder 64)
    - Bay Area Painting -- Condition Reports and Loan Receipts, 1984 January-October (Box II:5, Folder 65)
    - Bay Area Painting -- Newport and GAG Contract, 1984 February-March (Box II:5, Folder 66)
    - Bay Area Painting - The Figurative Mode (March 27-April 28), 1984 February-May (Box II:5, Folder 67)
    - Cocteau -- Correspondence, 1984 June 6-7 (Box II:5, Folder 68)
    - Cocteau -- to Miami/Return of Works not Traveling, 1984 June-July (Box II:5, Folder 69)
    - Cocteau -- Loan Fees/Crating Fees, 1984 April-August (Box II:5, Folder 70)
    - Cocteau -- Insurance, 1984 April-June (Box II:5, Folder 71)
    - Cocteau -- Condition Report/Loan Receipts, 1984 May-September (Box II:5, Folder 72)
    - Cocteau -- Customs, 1984 May (Box II:5, Folder 73)
    - Jean Cocteau -- Invitation, 1984 April (Box II:5, Folder 74)
    - Jean Cocteau -- Transportation, 1981 August-1982 October (Box II:5, Folder 75)
    - Jean Cocteau -- Travel, FAF, 1981 March-September (Box II:5, Folder 76)
    - Jean Cocteau -- Installation, 1984 May (Box II:5, Folder 77)
    - Jean Cocteau -- Loans Pending, 1983 January-1984 February (Box II:5, Folder 78)
    - Jean Cocteau -- Loans Confirmed, 1981 October-1984 April (Box II:5, Folder 79)
    - Jean Cocteau -- Funding, 1980 August-1984 January (Box II:5, Folder 80)
    - Jean Cocteau -- Project Budget, 1984 May 15-June 23 (Box II:5, Folder 81)
    - Cocteau -- US Loans, 1984 February-December (Box II:5, Folder 82)
    - Cocteau -- Packing Lists and Diag., 1984 November-1985 February (Box II:5, Folder 83)
    - Cocteau -- Foreign Loans, 1984 May (Box II:5, Folder 84)
    - Jean Cocteau and the French (May 15-June 23, 1984), 1984 February-June (Box II:5, Folder 85)
    - Jean Cocteau -- RRl File, 1982 July (Box II:5, Folder 86)
    - L'Atelier Mourlot -- Estimated Budget, 1984 February-September (Box II:5, Folder 87)
    - L'Atelier Mourlot -- Travel Vouchers, 1984 January-June (Box II:5, Folder 88)
    - Boldini -- Photograph Orders, 1983 April-1984 March (Box II:5, Folder 89)
    - Boldini -- Photo Bills, 1983 July-1984 September (Box II:5, Folder 90)
    - Boldini -- Dispersal, 1984 December-1985 April (Box II:5, Folder 91)
    - Boldini -- Ferrara, 1981 February-1984 October (Box II:5, Folder 92)
    - Boldini -- Couriers, 1984 October-1985 January (Box II:6, File 1)
    - Boldini -- Shipping, 1984 October-1985 May (Box II:6, File 2)
    - Boldini -- Catalogue, 1984 November-1985 January (Box II:6, File 3)
    - Boldini -- Correspondence, 1982 July-1984 November (Box II:6, File 4)
    - Boldini -- Correspondence with Gary Reynolds, 1984 April 13-September 26 (Box II:6, File 5)
    - Boldini -- Project Budget, 1984 (Box II:6, File 6)
    - Boldini -- Lady Abdy Collection, 1982 July-1983 November (Box II:6, File 7)
    - Boldini -- Valentin Abdy Collection, 1981 January-1983 October (Box II:6, File 8)
    - Boldini -- Rothschild, 1980 April-1981 November (Box II:6, File 9)
    - Boldini -- Megret Collection, 1981 January-October (Box II:6, File 10)
    - Boldini -- 1983 NEA Grant, 1983 June-1984 February (Box II:6, File 11)
    - Boldini -- Loans Confirmed (USA), 1982 July-1985 January (Box II:6, File 12)
    - Boldini -- Loans Confirmed (Europe), 1983 February-1985 February (Box II:6, File 13)
    - Boldini -- Loans Rejected, 1981 February-1984 June (Box II:6, File 14)
    - Boldini -- Insurance, 1983 September-1985 February (Box II:6, File 15)
    - Boldini -- Condition Reports and Loan Receipts, 1984 October-November (Box II:6, File 16)
    - Boldini -- Exhibit (Nov. 13-Dec. 22, 1984), 1984 October (Box II:6, File 17)
    - Boldini -- Social Segment (Portrait by Marcus Leatherdale), 1984 October-1985 January (Box II:6, File 18)
    - Boldini -- Miscellaneous, 1984 August-1985 February (Box II:6, File 19)
    - Small Gallery - Rene Santos "The Dog Show", 1985 January-February (Box II:6, File 20)
    - Action/Precision -- Contract, 1984 May-December (Box II:6, File 21)
    - Action/Precision -- Correspondence (1 of 2), 1984 May-1985 February (Box II:6, File 22)
    - Action/Precision -- Corespondence (2 of 2), 1984 July-1985 February (Box II:6, File 23)
    - Action/Precision -- Budget, Undated (Box II:6, File 24)
    - Action/Precision -- Crate List, 1984 April-1985 March (Box II:6, File 25)
    - Action/Precision -- Miscellaneous, 1983 September-1985 January (Box II:6, File 26)
    - Precious -- Uptown Galleries Loans, 1985 February-June (Box II:6, File 27)
    - Precious -- Mapplethorpe Studio Loan, 1985 February-May (Box II:6, File 28)
    - Precious -- Private Lenders, 1985 February-May (Box II:6, File 29)
    - Precious -- Soho Galleries Loans, 1985 February-May (Box II:6, File 30)
    - Precious -- East Village Galleries Loans, 1984 November-1985 June (Box II:6, File 31)
    - Precious -- Artist Loans, 1985 February-May (Box II:6, File 32)
    - Precious -- Loan Forms and Correspondence, 1985 February-September (Box II:6, File 33)
    - Precious -- Shipping and Insurance (1 of 2), 1985 February-May (Box II:6, File 34)
    - Precious -- Shipping and Insurance, 1985 February-May (Box II:6, File 35)
    - Precious -- Hand Delivered Works Checklist, 1985 March (Box II:6, File 36)
    - Precious -- Dispersal, 1985 May (Box II:6, File 37)
    - Precious -- Exhibition Expenses, 1985 (Box II:6, File 38)
    - Small Gallery -- Ruth Abrams, 1985 February-June (Box II:6, File 39)
    - Small Gallery -- Early Pop Drawings, 1985 April-June (Box II:6, File 40)
    - Small Gallery -- Early Pop Drawings, 1985 May-June (Box II:6, File 41)
    - Labyrinth -- Loan Agreement, 1985 May-October (Box II:6, File 42)
    - Labyrinth -- Installation and Shipping, 1985 April-July (Box II:6, File 43)
    - Alfredo Jaar, 1985 June-September (Box II:6, File 44)
    - Sol LeWitt -- Correspondence, 1985 May-August (Box II:6, File 45)
    - Sol LeWitt -- Condition Report, 1985 June-July (Box II:6, File 46)
    - Sol LeWitt -- Crate List, 1984 August-1985 June (Box II:6, File 47)
    - Sol LeWitt -- Transportation, 1985 April-September (Box II:6, File 48)
    - Indelible Image -- Correspondence, 1984 April-1986 May (Box II:6, File 49)
    - Indelible Image -- Correspondence and Shipping, 1985 February-December (Box II:6, File 50)
    - Indelible Image -- Grey Concoran Agreement, 1985 January-July (Box II:6, File 51)
    - Indelible Image -- Symposium, 1985 August-1986 January (Box II:6, File 52)
    - Josef Schutzenhofer Drawings - Small Gallery (War Photography), 1985 October-December (Box II:6, File 53)
    - Contemporary Indian Art -- Condition Reports and Insurance (1 of 2), 1985 October-1986 June (Box II:6, File 54)
    - Contemporary Indian Art -- Condition Report and Insurance (2 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box II:6, File 55)
    - Contemporary Indian Art -- Loan Agreement, Condition Reports, 1985-1986 (Box II:6, File 56)
    - Contemporary Indian Art -- Venue Correspondence, 1985 January-1986 March (Box II:6, File 57)
    - Contemporary Indian Art -- Other Correspondence, 1984 December-1986 July (Box II:6, File 58)
    - Contemporary Indian Art -- Indo-U.S. Subcommittee Correspondence and Expenses, 1984 August-1986 January (Box II:6, File 59)
    - Modern Redux/ICI -- Loans Approved, 1986 January-June (Box II:6, File 60)
    - Modern Redux/ICI -- Loans, 1986 (Box II:6, File 61)
    - Modern Redux/ICI -- Loans Rejected, 1986 April-June (Box II:6, File 62)
    - Modern Redux -- Loan Forms and Letters, 1985 December-1986 February (Box II:6, File 63)
    - Modern Redux -- Loan Forms for Credit Line, 1985-1986 (Box II:6, File 64)
    - Modern Redux -- Japanese Lenders, 1985 December-1986 September (Box II:6, File 65)
    - Modern Redux -- New York Lenders, 1985 January-1986 April (Box II:6, File 66)
    - Modern Redux -- European Lenders, 1985 December-1986 April (Box II:6, File 67)
    - Modern Redux -- USA/Canada Lenders, 1985 December-1986 May (Box II:6, File 68)
    - Modern Redux/ICI -- Problems, 1986 May-July (Box II:6, File 69)
    - Modern Redux -- Symposia, 1986 March 31 (Box II:6, File 70)
    - Modern Redux/ICI -- Correspondence, 1987 August 7 (Box II:6, File 71)
    - Modern Redux -- Fundraising Letters, 1986 January 13 (Box II:6, File 72)
    - Modern Redux -- Brademas Reception, 1986 March-April (Box II:7, File 1)
    - Modern Redux -- Architect. Leag. for Invitation, Undated (Box II:7, File 2)
    - Modern Redux -- Shipping, 1986 January-September (Box II:7, File 3)
    - Modern Redux -- Correspondence to Venues, 1985 August-December (Box II:7, File 4)
    - Modern Redux -- Symposia, 1986 January-April (Box II:7, File 5)
    - Modern Redux/ICI -- Correspondence, 1986 January-1987 May (Box II:7, File 6)
    - Modern Redux -- Works Not Traveling and Dispersal, 1986 July-November (Box II:7, File 7)
    - Modern Redux -- Donations to Exhibition (Correspondence and Thanks), 1986 March (Box II:7, File 8)
    - Modern Redux -- ICI Tour, 1986 April-September (Box II:7, File 9)
    - Modern Redux -- Post-Post Modern Architecture and Douglas Davis Miscellaneous (1 of 2), 1983 June-1986 January (Box II:7, File 10)
    - Modern Redux -- Post-Post Modern Architecture and Douglas Davis Miscellaneous (2 of 2), 1985 August-2001 March (Box II:7, File 11)
    - Modern Redux -- Miscellaneous, 1985 May-1986 April (Box II:7, File 12)
    - Small Gallery -- Todd Siler Works of Art, 1986 (Box II:7, File 13)
    - Small Gallery -- Todd Siler Works of Art, 1986 January-May (Box II:7, File 14)
    - Gallatin and His Circle -- Great Artists Fundraiser, Circa 1984-1986 (Box II:7, File 15)
    - Gallatin and His Circle Project, 1984 December-1985 August (Box II:7, File 16)
    - A. E. Gallatin and His Circle -- Loans, Insurance and Condition, 1985 April-1986 July (Box II:7, File 17)
    - Gallatin and His Circle -- Loans, 1986 February-May (Box II:7, File 18)
    - Gallatin and His Circle -- Miscellaneous, 1985 November-1986 May (Box II:7, File 19)
    - Robert Wilson -- Hamlet Machine (In Conjunction with Gallatin Exhibit), 1986 April-June (Box II:7, File 20)
    - Robert Wilson (In Conjunction with Gallatin Exhibition), 1986 May-July (Box II:7, File 21)
    - Abstract Appropriations (in Conjunction with Gallatin Exhibition), 1986 April-1987 December (Box II:7, File 22)
    - Abstract Appropriations -- Loans, 1986 April-July (Box II:7, File 23)
    - Rosalyn Drexler -- Correspondence, 1986 April-November (Box II:7, File 24)
    - Rosalyn Drexier -- Loans, 1986 April-1987 February (Box II:7, File 25)
    - Rosalyn Drexler -- Intimate Emotions (Greenville County, Sept. 9-Oct. 12, 1986), 1986 September (Box II:7, File 26)
    - Rosalyn Drexler -- Intimate Emotions (Greenville County, Sept. 9-Oct 12, 1986), 1986 August-December (Box II:7, File 27)
    - Rosalyn Drexler -- intimate Emotions (University of Iowa, Nov. 1-Jan. 11, 1987), 1986 June-1987 March (Box II:7, File 28)
    - Rosalyn Drexler -- Miscellaneous, 1986 June-1987 August (Box II:7, File 29)
    - Drexler and Abrams -- Shipping, 1986 May-September (Box II:7, File 30)
    - Rosalyn Drexler -- Condition Report Book, 1986-1987 (Box II:7, File 31)
    - Ruth Abrams -- Loans (July 10-August 28, 1989), 1986 May-September (Box II:7, File 32)
    - Ruth Abrams -- Paintings 1940-1985 (Condition Reports), Circa 1985-1986 (Box II:7, File 33)
    - Ruth Abrams -- Expenses, 1985 September-1986 July (Box II:7, File 34)
    - Ruth Abrams -- A Retrospective, 1986 March-August (Box II:7, File 35)
    - Arnulf Rainer -- Correspondence, 1985 September-1987 August (Box II:7, File 36)
    - Arnulf Rainer -- Cross Paintings, 1986 June-October (Box II:7, File 37)
    - Arnulf rainer -- Cross Paintings, 1986 July-October (Box II:7, File 38)
    - Arnulf Rainer -- Florida Atlantic University, 1985 October 25 (Box II:7, File 39)
    - Simon Linke -- Paintings (Small Gallery in Conj. with Rainer), 1986 July-November (Box II:7, File 40)
    - William Brice -- Correspondence, 1986 February-1987 January (Box II:7, File 41)
    - William Brice -- Correspondence, 1986 January-July (Box II:7, File 42)
    - William Brice -- Dinner, 1985 November-1987 March (Box II:7, File 43)
    - William Brice -- Dispersal and Shipping, 1986 October-1987 January (Box II:7, File 44)
    - Rick Horton -- Small Gallery Exhibition, 1986 December-1987 March (Box II:7, File 45)
    - Harrisons -- Correspondence, 1985 April-1987 May (Box II:7, File 46)
    - Harrison, Helen Mayer and Newton -- "Nobody Told Us When to Stop Thinking", 1987 March-October (Box II:7, File 47)
    - Harrisons -- Loans and Condition, 1987 March-April (Box II:7, File 48)
    - Paul Hunter -- White Noise (Small Gallery Exhibition) (Box II:7, File 49)
    - Awards in the Visual Arts -- Correspondence, 1985 May-1987 September (Box II:7, File 50)
    - Awards in the Visual Arts -- Shipping, 1987 March-June (Box II:7, File 51)
    - Awards in the Visual Arts -- Jill Giegerich Return (Lannan Foundation), 1987 June (Box II:7, File 52)
    - Awards in the Visual Arts -- Insurance, 1987 February-May (Box II:7, File 53)
    - Awards in the Visual Arts -- Miscellaneous, 1986 September-1987 September (Box II:7, File 54)
    - Pat Keck (Small Gallery in Conj. AVA), 1987 March-1988 January (Box II:7, File 55)
    - Pat Keck (Small Gallery in Conj. with AVA), 1987 April-June (Box II:7, File 56)
    - Out of eastern Europe -- Correspondence, 1987 February-September (Box II:7, File 57)
    - Out of Eastern Europe -- Contract, 1987 May (Box II:7, File 58)
    - Out of Eastern Europe -- Shipping, 1987 May-August (Box II:7, File 59)
    - Out of Eastern Europe -- Loan Agreement, 1987 May-August (Box II:7, File 60)
    - Ricardo Zulueta -- Cintas Fellowship, 1988 March 1 (Box II:7, File 61)
    - Ricardo Estanislao Zulueta -- Tableau Utopia, 1987 June-August (Box II:7, File 62)
    - Lee Gordon -- The Hooded Painting (Small Gallery Sept. 14-Oct. 24, 1987), 1987 August-October (Box II:7, File 63)
    - Lee Gordon -- The Hooded Paintings (Small Gallery Sept. 14-Oct. 24, 1987), 1987 August-November (Box II:7, File 64)
    - Morality Tales -- Correspondence, 1986 October-1989 January (Box II:7, File 65)
    - Morality Tales -- Correspondence, 1987 May-August (Box II:7, File 66)
    - Morality Tales -- NY Institute for the Humanities Talk (October 16), 1987 September 23 (Box II:7, File 67)
    - Morality Tales -- Video Project, 1987 October-November (Box II:7, File 68)
    - Morality Tales -- Dinner, 1987 August-September (Box II:7, File 69)
    - Morality Tales -- Tour Schedule, Circa 1986-1988 (Box II:7, File 70)
    - Morality Tales -- Shipping and Handling, 1987 August-October (Box II:7, File 71)
    - Morality Tales -- Photograph Permissions, 1987 September-November (Box II:7, File 72)
    - Morality Tales -- Contract, 1986 November 10 (Box II:7, File 73)
    - Morality Tales -- Insurance and Contract, 1986 November-1987 August (Box II:7, File 74)
    - Juan Gonzalez (Window Installation in Conj. with Morality Tales), 1987 August-November (Box II:7, File 75)
    - Jaar/Sheehan -- Correspondence, 1987 September-November (Box II:7, File 76)
    - Jaar/Sheehan -- Loans, 1986 December-1987 April (Box II:7, File 77)
    - Black Mountain College -- Correspondence, 1987 May-1988 March (Box II:7, File 78)
    - Black Mountain Collage -- Shipping, 1987 (Box II:8, Folder 1)
    - Black Mountain College -- Shipping and Installation, 1987 January-1988 March (Box II:8, Folder 2)
    - Black Mountain College -- Contract, 1986 June 5 (Box II:8, Folder 3)
    - Black Mountain College -- Loans, Insurance andn Facilities Reports, 1985 July-1988 January (Box II:8, Folder 4)
    - Gaylen Gerber (Small Gallery), 1987 September-1988 June (Box II:8, Folder 5)
    - Viollet-Le-Duc -- NEA and Related Miscellaneous, Undated (Box II:8, Folder 6)
    - Viollet-Le-Duc -- Correspondence, 1985 October-1988 April (Box II:8, Folder 7)
    - Viollet-Le-Duc -- Agreement, 1985 October-1986 December (Box II:8, Folder 8)
    - Viollet-Le-Duc --Shipping, 1987 December-1988 March (Box II:8, Folder 9)
    - Viollet-Le-Duc -- Insurance, 1976 July-1988 February (Box II:8, Folder 10)
    - Viollet-Le-Duc -- Stained Glass from the Cloisters (Small Gallery), 1987 August-1988 March (Box II:8, Folder 11)
    - Viollet-Le-Duc -- Stained Glass from the Cloisters (Small Gallery), 1987 December (Box II:8, Folder 12)
    - Cecil Beaton -- HMC Proposal, 1987 August-September (Box II:8, Folder 13)
    - Cecil Beaton -- Correspondence, 1986 September-1988 June (Box II:8, Folder 14)
    - Cecil Beaton -- Invitation Lists, Undated (Box II:8, Folder 15)
    - Cecil Beaton -- Mellor Lecture, 1988 March-April (Box II:8, Folder 16)
    - Cecil Beaton -- London Materials, 1987 July-1988 February (Box II:8, Folder 17)
    - Cecil Beaton -- Loans, Insurance and Shipping, 1988 January-May (Box II:8, Folder 18)
    - Cecil Beaton -- Budget and Agreements, 1987 July-December (Box II:8, Folder 19)
    - Cecil Beaton -- Miscellaneous, 1978 July-1988 March (Box II:8, Folder 20)
    - Rosalind Solomon -- Correspondence, 1986 November-1988 October (Box II:8, Folder 21)
    - Rosalind Solomon -- Contracts and Agreements, 1988 January-1990 October (Box II:8, Folder 22)
    - Rosalind Solomon -- Exhibition Tour, 1988 March-1989 April (Box II:8, Folder 23)
    - Rosalind Solomon -- Aids Support Organizations List, Circa 1988-1989 (Box II:8, Folder 24)
    - Rosalind Solomon -- Installation and Condition, 1988-1990 (Box II:8, Folder 25)
    - Rosalind Solomon -- Budget, 1987 September (Box II:8, Folder 26)
    - Rosalind Solomon -- Shipping, Returns and Other Miscellaneous, 1988 May-1995 March (Box II:8, Folder 27)
    - Eric Avery -- Works on Paper (Small Gallery), 1988 April-July (Box II:8, Folder 28)
    - Twelve From New York -- The 1988 Selections From the Nordstern Collection, 1987 November-1988 October (Box II:8, Folder 29)
    - Show and Tell -- Correspondence, 1981-1988 (Box II:8, Folder 30)
    - Show and Tell -- Budget, 1985 (Box II:8, Folder 31)
    - Show and Tell -- Financial and Other Miscellaneous, 1986 December (Box II:8, Folder 32)
    - Show and Tell -- Lenders List, 1988 September-October (Box II:8, Folder 33)
    - Show and Tell -- Institution Lenders (A-G), 1987 October-1989 January (Box II:8, Folder 34)
    - Show and Tell -- Institution Lenders (N-Z), 1987 October-1988 November (Box II:8, Folder 35)
    - Show and Tell -- Private Lenders, 1987 October-1988 November (Box II:8, Folder 36)
    - Show and Tell -- Lenders, 1987 November-1988 November (Box II:8, Folder 37)
    - Show and Tell -- Loan Rejections/Dropped, 1987 October-1988 March (Box II:8, Folder 38)
    - Show and Tell -- Lenders and Other Miscellaneous, 1987 October-1988 November (Box II:8, Folder 39)
    - Show and Tell -- Loans and Shipping, 1988 June-November (Box II:8, Folder 40)
    - Show and Tell -- Shipping (Pick Up), 1988 July-October (Box II:8, Folder 41)
    - Landmarks of NY -- Small Gallery (In Conj. with Show and Tell) (Box II:8, Folder 42)
    - Landmarks of NY -- Small Gallery (In Conj. with Show and Tell), 1988 August-September (Box II:8, Folder 43)
    - Luc Courchesue -- Encyclopedia Chiaroscuro, 1985-1988 (Box II:8, Folder 44)
    - Adolf Wolfli -- Correspondence, 1986 January-1989 February (Box II:8, Folder 45)
    - Adolf Wolfli -- Contract, 1988 May 23 (Box II:8, Folder 46)
    - Adolf Wolfli -- Shipping, 1988 October-1989 May (Box II:8, Folder 47)
    - Adolf Wolfli -- Invoices, 1988 October-November (Box II:8, Folder 48)
    - Shelly Bachman -- Small Gallery (In Conj. with Wolfli), 1988 October-1989 January (Box II:8, Folder 49)
    - Michael Landy, 1989 January-October (Box II:8, Folder 50)
    - French Revolution -- Proposed Exhibits (1 of 2), 1985-1988 (Box II:8, Folder 51)
    - French Revolution -- Proposed Exhibits (2 of 2), 1987 (Box II:8, Folder 52)
    - Politics and Polemics -- Correspondence, 1987 September-1989 March (Box II:8, Folder 53)
    - Politics and Polemics -- February 11 Dinner, 1989 February (Box II:8, Folder 54)
    - Politics and Polemics -- Contract, 1988 September-November (Box II:8, Folder 55)
    - Poletics and Polemics -- Shipping, 1988 September-1989 June (Box II:8, Folder 56)
    - Politics and Polemics -- NEH Proposal, 1987 (Box II:8, Folder 57)
    - Politics and Polemics -- Materials, 1985 June-1988 May (Box II:9, Folder 1)
    - Masami Teraoka -- Small Gallery, 1988 January-1989 April (Box II:9, Folder 2)
    - Masami Teraoka -- Small Gallery, 1988 January-1989 January (Box II:9, Folder 3)
    - Andy Warhol -- Correspondence, 1986 May-1990 August (Box II:9, Folder 4)
    - Andy Warhol -- NEH Proposal and Donna De Salvo Resume, 1986-1988 (Box II:9, Folder 5)
    - Andy Warhol -- Press Photos, Returns, Requests, 1989 January-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 6)
    - Andy Warhol -- Studio Museum/Pedestal, 1989 March-May (Box II:9, Folder 7)
    - Andy Warhol -- Guest List, 1989 February (Box II:9, Folder 8)
    - Andy Warhol -- Donna De Salvo Contract, 1988 February 3 (Box II:9, Folder 9)
    - Andy Warhol -- General Travel File, 1989 September-November (Box II:9, Folder 10)
    - Andy Warhol -- Shipping/Ollendorff (1st Tour: Carnegie, Serpentine, ICA), Circa 1989-1990 (Box II:9, Folder 11)
    - Andy Warhol -- Dispersal (1 of 2), 1990 April-1991 January (Box II:9, Folder 12)
    - Andy Warhol -- Dispersal (2 of 2), 1990 October (Box II:9, Folder 13)
    - Andy Warhol -- Tour (ICA, Carnegie, Serpentine), 1989 April-July (Box II:9, Folder 14)
    - Andy Warhol -- Traveling Venues (ICA, Philadelphia), 1989 April-1990 January (Box II:9, Folder 15)
    - Andy Warhol -- Traveling Venues (Carnegie Museum of Art), 1988 December-1989 November (Box II:9, Folder 16)
    - Andy Warhol -- Traveling Venues (Serpentine Gallery), 1989 January-1990 March (Box II:9, Folder 17)
    - Andy Warhol -- Traveling Venues (Foundation Cartier), 1989 December-1995 July (Box II:9, Folder 18)
    - Andy Warhol -- Traveling Venues (Newport Harbor Art Museum), 1989 September-1990 March (Box II:9, Folder 19)
    - Andy Warhol -- Traveling Venues (Lingotto, Turin), 1989 November-1990 October (Box II:9, Folder 20)
    - Andy Warhol -- Traveling Venues (Shipping/Extended Tour to Newport ,Turin, Versailles), 1989 December-1990 October (Box II:9, Folder 21)
    - Andy Warhol - Shipping ,Pickup and Returns of Objects Not Touring (February 1989), 1989 January-May (Box II:9, Folder 22)
    - Andy Warhol -- Works Not Traveling to Newport, Lingotte, Cartier, 1989 November-December (Box II:9, Folder 23)
    - Andy Warhol -- Works Not Traveling to Carnegie, Serpentine, ICA, 1988 December-1989 (Box II:9, Folder 24)
    - Andy Warhol -- Extended Loan List, Undated (Box II:9, Folder 25)
    - Andy Warhol -- Loans(Rejections/Dropped), 1988 June-1989 December (Box II:9, Folder 26)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lender Lists, Undated (Box II:9, Folder 27)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (John Ardoin), 1988 July-1992 February (Box II:9, Folder 28)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Alison Beyea), 1988 October-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 29)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Simeon Braguin), 1988 January-1989 December (Box II:9, Folder 30)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Stephen Bruce), 1988 November-1989 July (Box II:9, Folder 31)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Bruttal/Warhol Foundation), 1989 January-1990 July (Box II:9, Folder 32)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (John Butler), 1988 October-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 33)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Johnston and Carnegie), 1988 July-1989 December (Box II:9, Folder 34)